{
    "id": "dd123eb87f0a4e6b827840801524ac46",
    "title": "Last And The Last",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I had a discussion with him …………… week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "last",
                "the last"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ed9f7602757a4cbd880a1361286581ec"
        },
        {
            "question": "I think ………………… time I met him was when I was in Singapore.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "last",
                "the last",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "123995aa1c424d068864b07e375f954e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………….. met him in January.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "last",
                "the last",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d02593e5ad1e48fa8986277e0d9ee137"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had a cold ………………… week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "last",
                "the last",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e65f74bb0f604822b561654ecf47a115"
        },
        {
            "question": "Were you at the conference …………….. week?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "last",
                "the last",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d30cdab697564c7bb911412829081f5e"
        },
        {
            "question": "We bought this house …………….. year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "last",
                "the last",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "205b71a2f4fb4d2ab1aa4841df81c79a"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have lived here for …………….. year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "last",
                "the last",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bea1451585cc4068b4958dd754b0a04e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have been too busy for ……………. three months.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "last",
                "the last",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c09df941f61644cbada2b18ce66ffc15"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is ……………… car I buy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "last",
                "the last",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d147d4fefcd44826a8c10cb16679d1aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. few days have been very wet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Last",
                "The last",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e59823ca4bf64bf18cc471115e7c3c5a"
        }
    ]
}